Hello everyone!
I'm Saya Tanizaki, aka Saya-yan from not equal me!
Today, I'd like to introduce you to Saya Tanizaki's daily makeup routine!
I've participated in a lot of makeup projects on the Ikonoiju Channel,
I've participated in many makeup projects on the Ikonoiju Channel, but I've never introduced makeup every day, so I'm very, very nervous,
I'm very nervous, but I'd be very happy if you could all look at me warmly until the end!
Let's get started!
First of all, I've just finished putting on my base makeup, and I'm also wearing color contacts, so I'd like to introduce those as well.
These are color contacts produced by Ms. Sasahara,
They are Topaz Strawberry Quartz, and I have astigmatism, so I use astigmatism.
I have astigmatism, so I use astigmatism contacts. They are very natural, but they are very flattering and have a hint of pink in them, so I like them a lot and use them every day.
This is the pouch. It's big.
I would like to briefly introduce the base makeup,
First of all, here is the base makeup!
I may have mentioned this many times.
DIOR's Snow Makeup Base in blue.
Next, foundation.
SHU UEMURA's Ambimited Lasting Fluid, No. 594.
I really love the combination of this and this one, and I highly recommend it for a base makeup that never falls apart.
It tones up my face so much and I recommend it when you want to brighten up your face.
I also use two concealers.
I use one called DIOR Skin Forever Skin Correct Concealer.
It is a brighter color, but it really has great coverage and hides redness.
I recommend it.Recommendation.
Then the packaging came off after too much use,
I use a concealer called Creative Concealer by IPPO.
It's in a palette, and I'm embarrassed by the way it's used,
It comes in a palette, and I use that color the most often,
I really recommend it because it conceals fine details in certain areas.
Finally, I use Leblanc Skinlight Presto Powder N101 as a finishing powder.
So, I'd like to go ahead and actually do the makeup.
This is CAMMAKE, Chilkey Flair Eyez Matte Type M02.
I've introduced this one on the Iconoclast channel as well,
I really love this eyeshadow. I use the pink color on the upper right and the brown color on the lower left.
I take the color on the right arm here and apply it to the entire eyehall.
If you apply this too thickly, the color will come out really well,
I recommend applying it thinly over the entire eyelid, blending it out a little with your finger or something,
I recommend applying it thinly over the entire eyelid, blending it out with your finger or something.
I'm very excited to see it applied like this.
Here it is. It looks like this.
Next, take another brush and apply the brown one on the bottom left,
This makeup is really the biggest sticking point in my eye makeup,
I draw this triangular zone with brown, with the image of widening the width of the eye.
Like drawing an eyeliner line, like this.
Draw it like drawing an eyeliner line. First, draw above the zone you want to make into a triangle.
Draw like this.
With the intention of making the eyes bigger.
How do you feel? I felt that the width of my eyes had widened.What do you think? I feel like my eyes are getting wider and wider.
It looks really good.
Then, I would like to continue with the tear trough makeup.
This is Styr's Last Auto Gel Eyeliner No. 11.
This one is my favorite because it really emphasizes the tear troughs,
It's a highlighter-like pencil.
The entire tear trough is covered with this pencil.
I layered it on top of the tear ducts.
Like this.
Next, I would like to introduce the lame to be applied to the tear ducts.
It's in Street Yourself's eyeshadow palette #02.
This is a clothing brand,
I really love this eyeshadow,
I always apply the orange-ish color of this palette.
I always apply this color here, which is an orange-ish color.
I apply it all over.
The color is really cute and pretty,
I put on a thicker layer when I go to live shows.
What do you think?
It's done. Next, apply the same lame to the upper part of the black eye.
I applied the same lame to the upper part of the black eye. All over.
I recommend this because it gives a glittery, slightly glittery look. And next, I'm going to apply the eyeliner.
It's No. 05 in the One Day Tattoo Pro Cast the Eyeliner by Quare from Ske Palette. This one is sponsored by Noshita-san from the radio show,
The first time I used the eyeliner, it was really easy to draw and when I used it at a live show, it didn't break up.
I have been using this product for the past year or so. I draw it along my eye line to make my eyes droop just a little.I have been using this product for about a year now. I draw along my eye line to make my eyes droop just a little.
I only draw eyeliner on the outer corner of my eyes to make the width of my eyes look longer.
I want to make the width of my eyes look longer.
I draw diagonally.
I want to do the mascara last, but I want to do the mascara last because I want to see the balance of the whole body.
Next, I'm going to do my eyebrows with Selvorg's Indicate Eyebrow Powder, color #07.
It's a very pretty pink color.
I'm going to mix the bottom color with the pink in the middle, and I'm going to fill in the space between the eyebrows.
I like parallel brows.
I added more like this, and now my eyebrows look like this.
And the next one is Kizumi's heavy rotation coloring eyebrow No. 10.
My favorite color is pink, so I wanted to use pink all over my eyebrows.
This is just a little bit of pink, but I applied it just a little bit.
I applied it a little bit in the opposite direction, and then I applied it along the opposite side of the eyebrows.
If you apply it like this, you can get the color.
Okay, so the eyebrows are done. Next, I would like to do the blush.
Here is the blush.
It's Hince's Through Dimension Glow Blush No. G001.
It's a blush, but it's very shiny and bright.
It makes my skin look matte and bright.
I have matte skin, so this blush is great as a highlighter.
I love this blush because it can be used as a highlighter as well.
With a smiley face
I'll apply it right away.
The blush looks like this.Here's how the teak turned out.
Now we'd like to move on to sailing.
Sailing is here! I took off the package of this one too.
Sheer Matte Shading in Lilinew, No. 01 Glaze Tone.
I used the rightmost color more.
I'm going to use more of this color on the far right and less of the other colors overall.
It's a problem with my face.
Rather than applying it here
I apply more shading here than here.
I'm very particular about it.
Below...
I'd like to shave the nose a little bit using the same product here.
I'm going to take the lightest color in the middle and the darkest color on the right, and I'm going to apply it just a little bit below the eye socket.
Straight from here.
Here.
There's one more thing I want to mention.
Apply under the nose.
Apply it under the nose and a little above the tip of the nose.
Here.
I think it gives the impression of a little bit higher.
For the highlighter, I use the color 004 from Lior's Backstage Face Glow Palette.
I change it depending on the day, but I tend to use the upper left or lower left.
If I write the entire bridge of the nose, the nose will be emphasized, so I'm going to use the black side of the nose.
Here and
tip of the nose heretip of the nose here
Here. The tops of the eyes.
Here. Here.
Lip peak, here.
Next, here's the mascara base.
I use a mascara base called "All Day Fixing Mascara Base" by Milk Touch.
I recently started using this product because it holds my curl so well, but I have been using it for a long time now.
I applied the mascara base.
Next, mascara!
This is Heroine Makeup Volume Up Mascara in Super Waterproof No. 02.
Done! I didn't do anything on the left eye, and I applied primer and mascara on this one, but I think the volume is quite different.
And last but not least, the lipstick! Last but not least, lips! Today I would like to choose these two!
I got these two products when I was a part of an at-cosmetics shopping project by Econoize Channel,
First of all, here they are! Vivienne Laura's Lip Rouge Volupte Candy Glaze No. 6!
I applied it by pumping it on!
After that, I blended it a little with my finger!
It looks like this!
Here's where I'm going to make a special point...
This is the peak of my lips.
I think it's cuter if it's really tight here.
I put the Ipcho highlighter that I introduced at the beginning of this article.
I put the bottom color on the brush.
I'm going to draw the peak of the lips with this.
Yes!
Yes!Hmm!
I feel like I'm doing this all the time.
I feel like I have a bit of a duck mouth.
I'm drawing it.
Lastly, I'm going to use KURAZAS lip confort oil
I'm going to use #02.
My lips peel really easily.
So I'm going to moisturize them.
Mmm!
Yes!
So, my daily makeup is now complete!
The point of the makeup is to widen the width of the eyes,
I also add highlighter, lip peaks, and other points that I want to emphasize.
I would be very happy if I could be of some help to you, and I would be very happy if we could do the same makeup together.
Thank you so much for watching until the end!
Bye bye!